# JADA QUANDT

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **CONTACT**

C

770-401-4196



jadaquandt@gmail.com



Atlanta, GA



linkedin.com/in/ jadaquandt

## **EDUCATION**

Full-Stack Development
Certificate | DigitalCrafts Atlanta
| January-July 2020

B.A. in Journalism | Minor in Middle East Studies |Georgia State University |2008–2011

## **SKILLS**

- Debugging
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- Node.js
- Express
- React
- Redux
- RESTful API
- PostgreSQL
- Sequelize
- Bootstrap
- Adobe Photoshop

Additional details on prior work experience available upon request

#### **PROFILE**

Hardworking front-end developer with the desire and ability to learn new languages and technologies. Prior to becoming a front-end developer, I worked as an Executive Administrator for two municipalities, a church, and a salon where I managed subcontractors, volunteers, financial programs, and was required to become proficient and to train staff in many different software programs.

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT PORTFOLIO**

**Gym-Tan-Laundry** (May 2020) | gym-tan-laundry.herokuapp.com | github.com/digitalcrafts-atl/Gym-Tan-Laundry

- Member of a 5-person development team building a playlist development site that allows users to create a randomized playlist based on "Gym", "Tan", and "Laundry" categories.
- Primary responsibilities included assisting with Front-End design using EJS, learning and implementing Spotify's API parameters, writing the functions in JavaScript that populated and rendered playlists.
- Built with Bootstrap, JavaScript, RESTful API, Axios, Express, EJS, Passport JS. **Twitch Lyfe** (March 2020) | <u>twitchstreamlyfe.com.s3-website.us-east-1.amazonaws.com</u> | <u>github.com/jadaquandt/Twitch-Lyfe-Website</u>
  - Member of a 6-person development team building a Twitch website to feature the top streamers, top streamed games, and a search page to search the IGDB API to learn more about games.
  - Responsibilities included designing and assembling a fully mobile-responsive layout and creating the search page utilizing Javascript to render searches from the IGDB API
  - Built with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, RESTful API, and Axios.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

*Front Desk/Social Media Coordinator* | Darling & Co. Salon| Decatur, GA | October 2017 – January 2020

- Utilized Squarespace to create a new, simple website for the salon to easily update as needed.
- Arranged schedules for 11 individual stylists using Vagaro.
- Processed an average of 20 client payments daily with Square, etc.
- Maintained the salon's Facebook, Instagram, Yelp, and Google Business
- Photographed salon and stylists for website, promotions, and social media

**Public Works Administrator** | City of Brookhaven(Lowe Engineers) | Brookhaven, GA | October 2016-2017

- Processed an average of 30 citizen concerns daily using CitySourced software.
- Directed 10 subcontractors to fulfill work orders using Cityworks software.
- Created content and updated website to establish transparency for citizens

Church Administrator | Antioch Church | Woodstock, GA | October 2013-2016

- Achieved pastor's goal of digital overhaul of office and provided congregational education of new software.
- Arranged weekly volunteer and contractor team of 30+ using Planning Center.
- Established and managed church-wide budget using Quickbooks.
- Managed social media presence on Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and YouTube.